bladehq.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy - Blade HQ

**Effective Date: April 24, 2013**

Please read this privacy policy (this “

 _Privacy Policy_

”) carefully. Your use of 

_www.bladehq.com_

(the “

 _Website_

”) to access the Website and purchase products (the “

 _Products_

”) offered by 

_Blade HQ_

, LLC (“Blade HQ” or “

 _we_

” or “

 _our_

” or “

 _us_

”) on the Website, and your acceptance of the Terms and Conditions (the “Agreement”) by using the Website creates a binding, legal agreement between Blade HQ and you (“

 _you_

” or “

 _your_

”). Your access to the Website and purchase of Products shall be governed by the Agreement and also by this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy also describes how Blade HQ collects and uses information you post to the Website and provide to Blade HQ. The Agreement and this Privacy Policy may be collectively referred to as the Agreement, are intended to be read together, and in the event of conflict between the Agreement and this Privacy Policy, the terms of the Agreement shall prevail. Your use of the Website shall also become the effective date of this Privacy Policy (the “

 _Effective Date_

”). If you choose to accept this Privacy Policy, you must do so as written, without modification. If you do not accept this Privacy Policy, you will not be allowed to access the Website. By using the Website, you accept the terms and conditions described in this Privacy Policy. You warrant and represent that you are at least 18 years old and that you have the legal authority to enter into this Privacy Policy as an individual or on behalf of your employer. Blade HQ and you are individually, a “

 _party_

” and collectively, the “

 _parties_

.” 

**1\. Personal Information.** When purchasing Products, you agree to provide the information requested on the Website completely and accurately. As part of the purchase process, Blade HQ asks you to provide your name, a method by which to contact you (such as a telephone number or email address), your location, your age, the Products you wish to purchase, your credit card or debit card information, and other information. Additionally Blade HQ may request identification when a credit card payment is made. You are responsible for providing complete and accurate information (“

 _Personal Information_

”). Blade HQ may occasionally send informational emails, such as newsletters, to registered users. To opt out of these informational emails, please follow the “unsubscribe” directions in those emails. 

**2\. Updates to Privacy Policy. BLADE HQ RESERVES THE RIGHT TO AMEND THE WEBSITE AND THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY IN ITS DISCRETION FROM TIME TO TIME. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MONITORING THE WEBSITE FOR CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

**3\. Children’s Privacy.** The Website and the Products are directed to people who are at least 18 years old. Blade HQ does not knowingly collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are aware that Blade HQ has collected Personal Information from someone under the age of 18, please alert Blade HQ at [questions@bladehq.com](mailto:questions@bladehq.com) and the information will be removed from our system as soon as reasonably possible. Blade HQ does not knowingly aggregate or provide Public Information about people under the age of 18. 

**4\. Third Parties.** Except as expressly provided in this Privacy Policy, Blade HQ will not share your Personal Information with third parties without your permission. Blade HQ does not sell your Personal Information to third parties. Blade HQ may provide aggregate statistical information (such as the city or state in which you live) to third parties to describe Blade HQ’s services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. Blade HQ will not, however, disclose any personally identifiable information to these parties without your express permission or unless permitted by this Privacy Policy. 

You understand and agree that we monitor usage on the Website and the purchases of Products and that we may share your use of the Website and Services, including Personal Information, with law enforcement agencies and officials in response to inquiries or if we have reason to believe that your use of the Website and purchase of Products is for an unlawful purpose. We may also share your use of the Website and purchase of Products, including Personal Information, to third parties without your prior consent as required by law, a court order, a subpoena, legal process, governmental request, to investigate fraud, or as Blade HQ determines is necessary or advisable to protect its interests or your safety or the safety of others. 

We may also provide your Personal Information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as hosting provider or analytics provider or for the purpose of processing your form of payment, such as a credit or debit card. These companies are authorized to use your Personal Information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We will not be liable for their acts or omissions, and you shall hold us harmless for such acts or omissions.

If you have any questions about the ways in which Blade HQ protects your Personal Information, or if you wish to update or remove your Personal Information from Blade HQ’s database, please feel free to contact us at [questions@bladehq.com](mailto:questions@bladehq.com). 

We will retain your Personal Information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you Products. We will retain and use your Personal Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, as required by law, or for applicable statutes of limitations periods. Subject to your right to remove Personal Information as described below and our right to remove posted information in violation of the terms of this Privacy Policy, your posted information may remain on the Website as stated in this paragraph. Blade HQ reserves the right to remove your posted information at any time for any reason.

 **5\. Cookies.** Blade HQ uses cookies on the Website. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. When you login to Blade HQ the session ID cookie allows us to maintain a unique and secure (encrypted) connection with the user. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Blade HQ uses persistent session cookies to assist in navigation and for showing custom messages to you. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory. If you reject cookies, you may still use the Website, but your ability to use some areas of the Website, such as logging in, will be limited.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, and service providers is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, and service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate the Website.

**6\. Linking Policy.** The Website may contain links to other websites. Unless expressly stated, Blade HQ does not intend those links to be referrals or endorsements of the linked entities. These links are provided because they may be of interest to you and other Blade HQ users. Blade HQ is not responsible for the privacy policies or content of other websites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

Our Website may also include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, the Twitter button, or interactive mini-programs that run on the Website. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on the Website, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

You can also log in to the Website using sign-in services such as Facebook and Google. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on the Website to your profile page to share with others within your network.

**7\. Security.** The security of your Personal Information is important to Blade HQ. When you enter sensitive information such as a credit card number to purchase the Products, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Blade HQ follows generally accepted standards to protect the Personal Information you submit to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**8\. Posted Information.** Your voluntary disclosures of Personal Information on the Internet can be collected and used by others. Blade HQ will not, however, include any personally identifiable information on our message boards unless you specifically voluntarily include it in the content of your posting. To request removal of your Personal Information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [questions@bladehq.com](mailto:questions@bladehq.com). In some cases, Blade HQ may not be able to remove your Personal Information, in which case Blade HQ will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**9\. Term and Termination.** The term of this Privacy Policy shall begin on the Effective Date and continue until terminated as expressly provided in this Privacy Policy (the “

 _Term_

”). The Agreement and this Privacy Policy shall run concurrently and if either terminates, then the other shall automatically terminate. You may terminate this Privacy Policy at any time by delivering an email to Blade HQ at [questions@bladehq.com](mailto:questions@bladehq.com). Blade HQ may immediately terminate this Privacy Policy as required by law or due to your breach of any provision of this Privacy Policy in Blade HQ’s determination. Termination will become effective immediately. Upon termination, all license rights granted herein shall immediately terminate, and you will not be allowed to use the Website or Purchase Products. The following Sections of this Privacy Policy shall survive termination or expiration of this Privacy Policy for any reason: 8, 9, and 10.

**10\. Notice.** Except as expressly permitted herein, all other notices provided for herein shall be effected either by recognized international express courier, postage pre-paid, or by First Class United States Mail, postage pre-paid, to the address listed on the Website in our case, and to the address you listed in your registration page in your case. Notice shall be deemed received two days following tender to such courier and three days following posting by Mail. 

Blade HQ, LLC  
400 S. 1000 E. Suite E1  
Lehi, UT 84043  
Attn.: General Counsel
